export const CssData =[
    {
      "question": "What does CSS stand for?",
      "options": [
        "Creative Style Sheets",
        "Cascading Style Sheets",
        "Colorful Style Script",
        "Coded Style Script"
      ],
      "answer": 2
    },
    {
      "question": "Which of the following is NOT a valid CSS property?",
      "options": [
        "background-color",
        "font-weight",
        "text-decoration: none",
        "margin-left: 10px;" // Incorrect syntax
      ],
      "answer": 4
    },
    {
      "question": "How can you specify a rule to target all paragraph elements on a webpage?",
      "options": [
        "p {}",
        ".paragraph {}",
        "#paragraph {}",
        "all p {}",
      ],
      "answer": 1
    },
    {
      "question": "What is the purpose of the `!important` declaration in CSS?",
      "options": [
        "To define a global style",
        "To override inherited styles",
        "To create animations",
        "To add comments to code",
      ],
      "answer": 2
    },
    {
      "question": "Which of the following is a unit used to specify font size in CSS?",
      "options": [
        "pixels (px)",
        "em",
        "rem",
        "all of the above",
      ],
      "answer": 4
    },
    {
      "question": "What is the difference between `display: block` and `display: inline`?",
      "options": [
        "Block elements start on a new line, inline elements don't",
        "Block elements have width, inline elements don't",
        "Both are the same",
        "None of the above",
      ],
      "answer": 1
    },
    {
      "question": "How can you center an element horizontally using CSS?",
      "options": [
        "text-align: center",
        "margin: 0 auto",
        "float: center",
        "align: center",
      ],
      "answer": 2
    },
    {
      "question": "What is the role of a CSS pseudo-class like `:hover`?",
      "options": [
        "To define styles for specific elements",
        "To define styles for elements in a hover state",
        "To define global styles",
        "To create animations",
      ],
      "answer": 2
    },
    {
      "question": "What is the correct syntax to include an external stylesheet in an HTML document?",
      "options": [
        "<link rel='stylesheet' href='style.css'>",
        "<style src='style.css'></style>",
        "<stylesheet src='style.css'>",
        "None of the above",
      ],
      "answer": 1
    },
    {
      "question": "What is the benefit of using CSS preprocessors like SASS or LESS?",
      "options": [
        "Improved code organization and maintainability",
        "Ability to use variables and mixins",
        "Faster browser rendering",
        "Both A and B",
      ],
      "answer": 4
    }
  ]

  